The greatest guru that we have
Naszym największym Guru
is love.
jest miłość,
Sahaj love.
miłość Sahaj.
My father used to ask me : what do you dream?
Mój ojciec pytał mnie: "O czym marzysz?"
I said I want to meet all the seekers of the world,
Odpowiadałam, że chciałabym spotkać wszystkich poszukiwaczy na świecie,
that’s what I want, all over the world, all the nations.”
wśród wszystkich narodów świata, to jest to czego chcę.
This is the blessing of your own seeking.
To jest błogosławieństwo waszego poszukiwania.
Now the time has come for all of you to become Divine.
Teraz nadszedł ten czas, abyście wszyscy stali się Świętymi.
Enjoy yourself,
Cieszcie się sobą,
make others enjoy you.
sprawcie, żeby inni cieszyli się z wami.
Jai Mangal Murti
Jai Mangal Murti
You are all going to be very good children, alright?
Bądźcie dobrymi dziećmi, zgoda?
Girl: "I want a kiss for my birthday, for my birthday."
Dziewczynka: "Ja poproszę buziaka na urodziny, na urodziny".
Today? Oh! Many happy returns of the day.
To dzisiaj, ojej! Wszystkiego najlepszego z okazji urodzin.
Now let everyone coming for kisses alright?
A teraz niech każdy przyjdzie po całusa.
Come. Now all those who had kiss, should go back.
Podchodźcie. Ci, którzy dostali całusa, powinni przejść do tyłu.
Watch your parents, alright?
Opiekujcie się swoimi rodzicami.
Paolo is coming now.
Paolo już idzie.
He kissed me, you all kissed me, alright?
On już mnie ucałował, wszyscy już mnie ucałowali.
This one didn’t ? Alright.
A ten jeden nie?
Thank you, thank you very much, may God bless you all.
Dziękuję, dziękuję bardzo. Niech was wszystkich Bóg błogosławi.
Now, we are facing little children.
Jeśli chodzi o małe dzieci,
They are the ones who are incarnations.
one są inkarnacjami.
They are the ones who are going to lead humanity
One poprowadzą ludzkość
into some great advancement.
na wyższy poziom.
The humanity has to be looked after.
Ludzkością trzeba się zaopiekować.